Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪No one can stop us, we rise through the storm♪
♪لا أحد يستطيع إيقافنا، نحن ننهض من خلال العاصفة♪
♪Even bleeding and broken, we'll still push on♪
♪حتى مع النزيف والكسر، سنستمر في المضي قدمًا♪
♪The earth quakes with furious might♪
♪تهتز الأرض بقوة شديدة♪
♪I'll hold your hand and charge into the light♪
♪سأمسك بيدك وأتجه نحو النور♪
♪Adventurers, a new tale begins♪
♪المغامرون، تبدأ قصة جديدة♪
♪Brave hearts in the real world win♪
♪القلوب الشجاعة تفوز في العالم الحقيقي♪
♪Sparks fly when courage collides♪
♪تتطاير الشرر عندما تلتقي الشجاعة♪
♪Burning bright, our crystal tears ignite♪
♪تحترق بشدة، وتشتعل دموعنا البلورية♪
♪Above this city we stand tall♪
♪ فوق هذه المدينة نقف شامخين ♪
♪Flying wild, we're breaking every wall♪
♪نطير في البرية، ونكسر كل الجدران♪
♪Love's grand adventure, we'll conquer it all♪
♪مغامرة الحب الكبرى، سوف نتغلب عليها جميعًا♪
=Keeping Up with Beauty= (Adapted from "The Highborn Matron Reborn as the Pitiful Heiress")
=مواكبة الجمال= (مقتبس من "السيدة النبيلة التي ولدت من جديد وريثة بائسة")
=Episode 19=
=الحلقة 19=
This is for you.
هذا لك.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
What's on your mind?
ما الذي يدور في ذهنك؟
You seem distracted.
يبدو أنك مشتت.
Haven't you found that jade pendant?
ألم تجد تلك القلادة اليشمية؟
It's alright.
لا بأس.
You've reclaimed the hotel after all.
لقد استعدت الفندق بعد كل شيء.
I'll help you look for the jade pendant.
سأساعدك في البحث عن قلادة اليشم.
No matter what it takes,
بغض النظر عما يتطلبه الأمر،
I'll find it for you.
سأجده لك.
Oh, right.
أوه، صحيح.
I've got another gift for you.
لدي هدية أخرى لك.
It's my silver spear!
إنه رمحي الفضي!
I found this at the black market.
وجدت هذا في السوق السوداء.
I just thought of trying my luck.
لقد فكرت فقط في تجربة حظي.
To my surprise, I found it there.
لقد فوجئت عندما وجدته هناك.
This is considered a thousand-year-old antique.
تعتبر هذه قطعة أثرية عمرها ألف عام.
I bet it was expensive.
أراهن أنها كانت باهظة الثمن.
I can't accept it.
لا أستطيع قبول ذلك.
Just take it.
فقط خذها.
It belongs to you anyway.
فهو ملك لك على أية حال.
Also, don't you think it's all fated?
ألا تعتقد أيضًا أن الأمر كله مقدر؟
Even though a millennium has passed,
على الرغم من مرور ألف عام،
some cherished objects remain reclaimable.
تظل بعض الأشياء العزيزة قابلة للاستعادة.
Thank you, then.
شكرا لك إذن.
Muyan.
مص.
You've done more than enough for me.
لقد فعلت أكثر مما يكفي بالنسبة لي.
In fact, you need not treat me so well.
في الواقع، ليس عليك أن تعاملني بشكل جيد.
Have you forgotten this, General?
هل نسيت هذا يا سيدي الجنرال؟
You saved my life.
لقد انقذت حياتي.
Don't let him get away!
لا تدعه يفلت من بين يديك!
Quick! Give chase!
سريعًا! طارد!
Over there!
هناك!
Stop right there!
توقف هنا!
Everyone, get up!
الجميع، استيقظوا!
Hurry up!
عجلوا!
Give chase now!
إذهب للمطاردة الآن!
Stop running!
توقف عن الجري!
Stop right there!
توقف هنا!
You're a pretty good runner, huh?
أنت عداء جيد جدًا، أليس كذلك؟
You wanted to report that to the official, huh?
أردت أن تبلغ المسؤول بذلك، أليس كذلك؟
Dream on!
إحلم!
Get rid of him!
تخلص منه!
Go! Let's go now!
إذهب! دعنا نذهب الآن!
- Let's go. - Go.
- دعنا نذهب. - اذهب.
I've dealt with those bullies.
لقد تعاملت مع هؤلاء المتنمرين.
You're no longer a runaway after this.
لن تصبح هاربا بعد هذا.
Go home.
اذهب إلى المنزل.
If you have nowhere to be,
إذا لم يكن لديك مكان لتكون فيه،
join my army, then.
انضم إلى جيشي إذن.
Thank you so much.
شكراً جزيلاً.
Nice one!
هذا لطيف!
One more time!
مرة أخرى!
I see.
أرى.
It was you!
لقد كنت أنت!
General.
عام.
Please allow me
من فضلك اسمح لي
to treat you well forever.
أن أعاملك بشكل جيد إلى الأبد.
Just leave such matters to Mr. Shen.
فقط اترك مثل هذه الأمور للسيد شين.
That won't do.
هذا لن يفعل.
It's too personal of a matter.
إنها مسألة شخصية للغاية.
The elevator isn't working today.
المصعد لا يعمل اليوم.
We have to use the stairs.
علينا أن نستخدم السلالم.
Greetings, Mr. Gu.
تحياتي السيد جو.
Hi.
أهلاً.
Slowly.
ببطء.
Chenyu.
لك.
I'm sorry,
أنا آسف،
but I forgot the keys.
ولكنني نسيت المفاتيح.
I'll take them now. I'll be back soon.
سآخذهم الآن. سأعود قريبًا.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Greetings, Mr. Gu.
تحياتي السيد جو.
Hi.
أهلاً.
You're still here, Mr. Gu.
أنت لا تزال هنا، السيد جو.
Bye.
الوداع.
Mr. Gu.
السيد جو.
Do you need any help?
هل تحتاج إلى أي مساعدة؟
Just get back to work.
فقط العودة إلى العمل.
Yes.
نعم.
Greetings, Mr. Gu.
تحياتي السيد جو.
Mr. Gu!
السيد جو!
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
What's this?
ما هذا؟
Are you alright, Mr. Gu?
هل أنت بخير، سيد جو؟
Chenyu!
لك!
Are you okay, Chenyu?
هل أنت بخير، تشنيو؟
Shiqi.
شيكي.
Help me up.
ساعدني على النهوض.
Mr. Gu.
السيد جو.
It's me, Ruyin.
أنا رويين.
Can't you see me?
ألا تستطيع رؤيتي؟
He can't see us?
هل لا يستطيع رؤيتنا؟
What's the matter with Mr. Gu?
ما الأمر مع السيد جو؟
How did he fell down the stairs?
كيف سقط من الدرج؟
He can't see us.
لا يستطيع رؤيتنا.
Has he gone blind?
هل أصبح أعمى؟
Do you want us to get you an ambulance, Mr. Gu?
هل تريد منا أن نرسل لك سيارة إسعاف، سيد جو؟
(Gu Group recently released a statement saying)
(أصدرت مجموعة Gu مؤخرًا بيانًا قالت فيه)
(that its CEO, Gu Chenyu, has suspended all work)
(أن الرئيس التنفيذي للشركة، جو تشين يو، أوقف جميع أعماله)
(due to sudden blindness.)
(بسبب العمى المفاجئ.)
(According to an insider,)
(وفقا لمصدر مطلع)
(Gu Chenyu's vision problems are very serious.)
(مشاكل الرؤية لدى Gu Chenyu خطيرة للغاية.)
(He fell down the stairs in public and lost consciousness.)
(سقط على الدرج أمام العامة وفقد وعيه.)
Chenyu...
لك...
(His current condition remains unknown.)
(حالته الحالية لا تزال غير معروفة.)
I didn't want you to hear any of this,
لم أكن أريدك أن تسمع أي شيء من هذا،
but I think
ولكنني أعتقد
since it concerns the company,
حيث أن الأمر يتعلق بالشركة،
you should at least know about it.
ينبغي عليك أن تعرف ذلك على الأقل.
But don't worry.
ولكن لا تقلق.
I'll handle all the public opinion issues.
سأتعامل مع كافة قضايا الرأي العام.
For now, the most important thing for you is to rest well
في الوقت الحالي، أهم شيء بالنسبة لك هو أن تحصل على قسط جيد من الراحة.
and take care of your eyes.
واعتني بعينيك.
I'll head to work now.
سأذهب إلى العمل الآن.
If you need anything, just ask the housekeeper.
إذا كنت بحاجة إلى أي شيء، فقط اسأل مدبرة المنزل.
Let me do it.
دعني افعل ذلك.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I heard you fell down the stairs.
سمعت أنك سقطت من على الدرج.
Are you here to mock at me?
هل أنت هنا للسخرية مني؟
Yeah.
نعم.
After years of scheming,
بعد سنوات من التخطيط،
in the end, you got nothing.
في النهاية، لم تحصل على شيء.
You should leave.
ينبغي عليك أن تغادر.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Gu Chenyu.
قو تشينيو.
Can you stop making me worry?
هل يمكنك التوقف عن جعلني أشعر بالقلق؟
I'll stay and help you
سأبقى وأساعدك
until you get better.
حتى تتحسن حالتك.
I don't need your pity.
لا أحتاج إلى شفقتك.
Gu Chenyu.
قو تشينيو.
I've seen countless people worse off than you.
لقد رأيت عددًا لا يحصى من الأشخاص أسوأ حالًا منك.
Their families have been torn apart.
لقد تمزقت عائلاتهم.
They are homeless
إنهم بلا مأوى
and physically disabled.
والمعوقين جسديا.
Every one of them is more miserable than you.
كل واحد منهم أكثر بؤسًا منك.
Someone like you
شخص مثلك
doesn't deserve my sympathy.
لا يستحق تعاطفي.
Then why are you back here?
إذن لماذا عدت إلى هنا؟
I...
أنا...
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
He was stabbed because of me.
لقد طُعن بسببي.
He can't see now.
لم يعد يستطيع الرؤية الآن.
I'd like to stay here until his recovery.
وأود أن أبقى هنا حتى يتعافى.
Suit yourself.
تناسب نفسك.
♪Words I can't say linger on my tongue♪
♪الكلمات التي لا أستطيع قولها تبقى على لساني♪
♪Each time you're near, my heartbeat runs♪
♪في كل مرة تكون بالقرب، ينبض قلبي♪
♪Cold nights glow with gentle stars above♪
♪الليالي الباردة تتوهج بالنجوم اللطيفة في الأعلى♪
♪My silent thoughts stretch long like dreams of love♪
♪أفكاري الصامتة تمتد طويلاً مثل أحلام الحب♪
♪How do I hide these feelings so faint and shy♪
♪كيف أخفي هذه المشاعر بهذا القدر من الخجل والضعف♪
♪When I meet you again, warmth flows quietly by♪
♪عندما ألتقي بك مرة أخرى، يتدفق الدفء بهدوء♪
♪My eyes can't help but turn your way♪
♪لا يمكن لعيني إلا أن تتجه نحوك♪
♪I close them tight, pretending all is the same♪
♪أغلقهم بإحكام، وأتظاهر بأن كل شيء متشابه♪
♪The wind brushes softly by♪
♪تمر الرياح برفق♪
♪Carrying half of my sigh♪
♪أحمل نصف تنهيدة♪
♪I walk a while, then glance behind♪
♪أمشي لفترة، ثم أنظر خلفي♪
♪You bring back warmth I thought I'd lost♪
♪لقد أعادت لي الدفء الذي اعتقدت أنني فقدته♪
♪My pain quietly thaws♪
♪يذوب ألمي بهدوء♪
♪And in silence, loneliness fades away♪
♪وفي الصمت يتلاشى الشعور بالوحدة♪
♪Because you are my light in the dark♪
♪لأنك نوري في الظلام♪
♪I'll be your sun when winter feels too hard♪
♪سأكون شمسك عندما يصبح الشتاء قاسيًا جدًا♪
♪We shine for each other through the quiet and the loneliness♪
♪نحن نتألق لبعضنا البعض من خلال الهدوء والوحدة♪
♪You are the warmest light in all my world♪
♪أنت أدفأ ضوء في عالمي كله♪